H. Alexander Smith Papers, 1897-1966 (bulk 1920-1966 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 2: Relief Work and Princeton University, 1915-1934; 25.44 linear feet 61 boxes
  - Subseries 2C: Princeton University, Administration and Faculty, 1915-1934; 11.05 linear feet 26.5 boxes
    - Executive Secretary, 1915-1934; 20 boxes
      - Cap and Gown Club, Constitution and By-Laws, 1923; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Carnegie Foundation, 1926-1927; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Chapel, 1921-1934; 5 folders
        - Correspondence, 1921-1930; 2 folders
          - 1921-1926, 1 folder (Folder 1)
          - 1926-1930, 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Daily, 1926-1927; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Sunday Evening Talks, 1930; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Weddings and Baptisms, 1931-1934; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Chemistry Department, 1925-1927; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Commencement Committee, 1923-1925; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Classics Department, 1924; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Controller’s Office, 1922-1923; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Course of Study Committee, 1923; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Curriculum Committee, 1920-1930; 3 boxes (2 partial)
        - Correspondence, 1921-1930; portions of 2 boxes
          - 1921-1922, 1 folder (Folder 11)
          - 1922-1924, 1 folder (Folder 1)
          - 1924-1925, 1 folder (Folder 2)
          - 1926-1927, 1 folder (Folder 3)
          - 1928-1930, 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Reports, 1920-1922; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Reports, 1920-1927; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Cutting, James Russell, 1928-1930; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Dean of Faculty, 1926-1929; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Discussion Group, 1924-1927; 2 folders
        - 1924-1927, 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - 1926-1927, 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Economics Department, 1920-1927; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Engineering Department, 1917-1928; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - English Department, 1923-1927; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Examinations and Standing, 1923-1927; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - European Trip, 1930; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Faculty, 1920-1930; 5 folders
        - Committees, 1929-1930; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Correspondence, 1920-1922; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Development, 1920-1922; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Housing, 1924-1927; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Salary Issue, 1926-1927; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Fentress, Calvin, 1927-1929; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Finance Committee, 1920-1929; portions of 2 boxes
        - Correspondence, 1920-1929; portions of 2 boxes
          - 1920-1923, 1 folder (Folder 8)
          - 1923-1925, 1 folder (Folder 9)
          - 1925-1929, 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Frick Estate, 1925-1926; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Minutes, 1920-1927; 3 folders
          - 1920-1922, 1 folder (Folder 3)
          - 1922-1925, 1 folder (Folder 4)
          - 1925-1927, 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Financial Advisers, 1920-1923; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Football Games, 1924-1926; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Fort Morrow Campaign, 1930; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Graduate School, 1920-1927; 3 folders
        - 1920-1927, 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - 1921-1922, 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - 1926-1927, 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - General Statement of Policy, Plan and Needs, 1925-1926; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Geology Department, 1926; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Grounds and Buildings Committee, 1915-1927; 3 folders
        - Correspondence, 1920-1925; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Correspondence, 1925-1927; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Minutes, 1915-1923; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - History and Politics Department, 1920-1927; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Honorary Degrees Committee, 1924-1927; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - House at Princeton, Rejected Plans, 1925; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Hygiene Department, 1926; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - International Law, Notes, 1928; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - International Relations, 1927-1930; 3 boxes (2 partial)
        - General, 1928-1929; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - General, 1928-1930; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Clippings, 1930; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Correspondence, 1929-1930; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Lecture Notes, 1929-1930; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Library, 1929-1930; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Material, 1929-1930; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Pamphlets, 1927-1928; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Questionnaire, 1929-1930; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Reports of Committees, 1929-1930; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Seminar, 1930; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Yale Conference, 1930; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Kingston-New Brunswick Turnpike, 1923; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Kirk, Doctor, 1923; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Law School at Princeton, 1922-1924; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - League of Nations, Pamphlets, 1927-1930; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Lectures, 1920-1930; 3 folders
        - 1920-1924, 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - 1926-1927, 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - 1929-1930, 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Library Committee, 1925-1927; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Limitations of Students, 1921-1922; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Mathematical Society, 1924-1925; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Memos to the President, 1920-1924; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Modern Language Department, 1922-1924; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Municipal Government, Notes, 1920-1921; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - National Council on Religion in Higher Education, 1924-1926; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - National Student Federation, 1926-1927; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - National Woodrow Wilson Memorial Association, 1925-1926; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Naval Department, 1929-1930; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Notes on Europe, 1927-1928; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Pamphlets, Miscellaneous, 1930-1931; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Philadelphian Society, 1923-1926; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Philosophy Department, 1919-1925; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Politics Department, 1927-1930; portions of 2 boxes
        - American Politics, 1928-1929; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Books, 1927-1929; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Constitutional Government, 1928-1929; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Correspondence, 1927-1929; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Correspondence, 1929-1930; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Jurisprudence, 1928-1929; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Foreign Relations, 1928-1929; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - President Hibben, 1926-1930; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Princeton-Harvard Relations, 1926-1928; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Princeton-in-Peking, 1925-1931; portions of 2 boxes
        - 1925-1926, 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - 1926-1929, 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - 1929-1930, 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - 1930-1931, 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Princeton Trademark Issues, 1923-1925; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Prohibition, 1923-1924; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Psychology Department, 1920-1925; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Public Lectures Committee, 1928-1930; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Recommendations, 1925-1926; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Religion Department, 1928; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Religious Education, 1926-1930; portions of 2 boxes
        - Buchmann, Frank, Clippings and Pamphlets, 1927-1928; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Buchmann, Frank, Correspondence, 1926-1930; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Case, Everett, 1928; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - Clippings, 1928-1930; 1 folder (Folder 12)
        - Clippings and Pamphlets, 1928-1929; 1 folder (Folder 13)
        - Fentress, Calvin, 1928-1930; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Gardner, O. F, 1928; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - The Independent, 1928; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Purdy, Ray F, 1928-1929; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Raven, Canon Charles E, 1928-1929; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Shoemaker, Reverend S. M. Jr, 1928-1929; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1927-1930; 3 folders
          - 1927-1930, 1 folder (Folder 7)
          - 1929-1930, 1 folder (Folder 8)
          - 1930, 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Resignation, 1927-1932; 3 folders
        - Correspondence, 1927; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Correspondence, 1932; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - Statement of Reasons, 1930; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Reorganization Program, 1923-1925; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Requests for Names for College Presidents, 1923-1925; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Robert College, 1931-1932; portions of 2 boxes
        - Correspondence, 1931-1932; 1 folder (Folder 15)
        - Pamphlets, 1931; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Report, 1932; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Turkey Trip, 1931; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - School of Public Affairs, 1929-1930; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Secretary, 1926-1928; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Secretaryship of the University, 1920; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Senior Council, 1919-1927; 2 folders
        - 1919-1925, 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - 1926-1927, 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Statistics, 1921-1927; 3 folders
        - 1921-1922, 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - 1921-1925, 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - 1926-1927, 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Sterling Educational Bill, 1923-1924; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Student Aid Associations, 1923-1925; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Student Employment, 1926-1927; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Student Investigations, 1923-1926; 2 folders
        - 1923-1924, 1 folder (Folder 15)
        - 1923-1926, 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Students of Interest, 1919-1930; 3 folders
        - 1919-1926, 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - 1922-1926, 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - 1929-1930, 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Summer School, 1923-1924; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Undergraduate Life, 1922-1930; 3 folders
        - 1922-1927, 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - 1928-1929, 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - 1929-1930, 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - University Budgets, 1924-1927; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Visitors to Princeton, 1924 October; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Whig and Clio Halls, 1921-1924; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Will the College Survive?, Drafts, 1931; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Wilsoniana Collection, 1924; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Woods, Lawrence C, 1924-1925; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - World Court, 1923-1925; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous, 1915-1933; 2 boxes (1 partial)
        - 1915-1931, 1 folder (Folder 15)
        - 1922-1923, 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - 1927, 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - 1930, 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - 1931-1933, 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous, undated; 1 item
- Series 3: New Jersey Politics, 1919-1945; 50.46 linear feet 121 boxes
  The New Jersey Politics Series documents Smith’s time as a private citizen after leaving his position at Princeton and before he held elected office. Smith worked as a lawyer during this period and remained actively involved in the New Jersey Republican Party. The bulk of the material in this series relates to Republican Party affairs in New Jersey. Also included are personal documents such as correspondence, financial papers and materials related to Smith’s legal career.
  The New Jersey Politics Series is divided into four subseries: New Jersey State Republican Affairs, Personal, Public Issues, and Public Relations. The subseries are arranged alphabetically.
  - Subseries 3A: New Jersey State Republican Affairs, 1930-1944; 27.52 linear feet 66 boxes
    The New Jersey State Republican Affairs Subseries consists mainly of documents created while Smith was chairman of the 2nd Region Program Committee of the Republican Party and the treasurer of the New Jersey Republican State Committee. As a result, this subseries offers a unique perspective on the history of the New Jersey Republican Party from the New Deal era through the start of World War II. Documents include meeting minutes, memoranda, press releases and reports discussing platforms and strategy, campaign literature, correspondence between Smith and local Republican candidates running for elected office, correspondence to and from the New Jersey constituency and party members, and correspondence and printed matter related to national candidates. Many of the key issues of the day are discussed at length including the Republican Party’s policies on labor, social security and civil rights, the party’s anti-New Deal efforts, America’s place in relief efforts abroad, amendments to New Jersey’s state constitution, and prohibition in New Jersey.
    The New Jersey State Republican Affairs Subseries is arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - American Liberty League, 1935-1936; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Commissioner of Finance, 1934; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1935-1940; 2 folders
      - M-O, 1935-1940; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - P-R, 1935-1940; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - Mercer County, 1933-1934; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - New Jersey Constitution, Pamphlets, 1935; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - New Jersey Republican Council, 1933-1935; portions of 2 boxes
      - Appeal for Contributions, 1935 February-June; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Campaign Materials, 1934; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1933-1935; 3 folders
        - General, 1934-1935; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Gumb, Irving T, 1934-1935; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous, 1933-1934; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Executive Committee, 1934-1935; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Newspaper Clippings and Printed Material, 1934; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous, 1933; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Newark Star Eagle, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1936-1938; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - Norman, Leonard, Executive Secretary, 1936-1940; portions of 2 boxes
      - Correspondence, 1936-1937; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1939-1940; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Platform Material, 1934-1938; 4 folders
      - 1934, 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - 1935, 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - 1937, 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - 1938, 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Pomeroy, Daniel E., Luncheons, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    - Pomeroy, Daniel E., Correspondence, 1935-1940; 1 folder (Folder 8)
    - Republican National Committee, 1935-1941; 3 boxes (2 partial)
      - Campaigns, 1940; portions of 2 boxes
        - Convention, 1940; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Dewey, Thomas, 1940; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Taft, Robert, 1940; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Willkie, Wendell, 1940; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1935-1941; 3 folders
        - General, 1935-1936; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - General, 1938-1941; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Works Progress Administration, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Hamilton, J. D. M, 1936-1939; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Platforms, 1936-1940; portions of 2 boxes
        - Drafts, 1936; 2 folders (Folder 8 to 9)
        - Miscellaneous, 1940; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Republican Program Committee, 1932-1942; 26 boxes (2 partial)
      - Addresses, 1937-1939; 7 folders
        - Chairman’s Address, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Governor of Maryland, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Material, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Quo Vadis Republicans?, 1937; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Summer Conference, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Vineland, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Miscellaneous, Notes, 1937-1938; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Civil Service, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Committees, 1937-1941; 4 boxes (1 partial)
        - Agriculture, 1938-1939; portions of 2 boxes
          - Correspondence, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 11)
          - Memos and Pamphlets, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 12)
          - Work Plan, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 1)
          - Miscellaneous, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Banking and Currency, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Banking and Currency, 1941; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Business and Government, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Business and Government, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Civic and Political Liberty, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Finance, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Finance, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Foreign Policy, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Foreign Relations, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Fundamentals, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Labor, 1937; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Labor, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Membership Lists, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Reciprocity, Soaps and Glycerin, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Social Well-Being, 1938-1939; more than 8 folders
          - Civil Rights, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 3)
          - Committee Meetings, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 4)
          - Health Care, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 5)
          - Housing, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 6)
          - Labor, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 7)
          - Relief, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 8)
          - Social Security, 1938-1939; 2 folders (Folder 9 to 10)
          - Miscellaneous, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - Young Women’s School of Political Science, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 12)
        - Youth, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, 1935-1942; 5 boxes
        - General, 1938-1942; 3 boxes (1 partial)
          - 1938-1939, 3 boxes (1 partial)
            - A-B, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 1)
            - Brown, Calvin, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 2)
            - C, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 3)
            - D-G, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 4)
            - Gardner, O. F., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 5)
            - H-L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 1)
            - M-N, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 2)
            - O-P, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 3)
            - R-Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 1)
          - 1939 January-August, 1 folder (Folder 2)
          - 1940, 1 folder (Folder 3)
          - P-Y, 1940-1942; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Baird and Smith, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Buell, Raymond, 1939-1940; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Financial, 1937-1939; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Flanders, R. E, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Frank, Glenn, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Hamilton, John, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Hope, Walter, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Howe, William, 1939-1940; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Lovejoy, Frank W, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Miller, Spencer, Jr, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Prentis, H. W., Jr, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Shaw, Arch W, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Volunteer Workers, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Windels, Paul, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Young Republicans Club, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous, 1935-1940; 2 boxes (1 partial)
          - 1938, 1 folder (Folder 11)
          - 1938-1939, 1 folder (Folder 1)
          - 1938-1940, 1 folder (Folder 2)
          - 1939-1940, 1 folder (Folder 3)
          - S-U, 1935-1940; 1 folder (Folder 4)
          - V-Z, 1935-1940; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Drafts, 1938-1940; 5 boxes (1 partial)
        - General, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Committee Report, 1939; 2 folders (Folder 2 to 3)
        - Criticisms, Paul Windels, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Final, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Final, 1940; 2 folders (Folder 1 to 2)
        - Frank, Glenn, 1939 October; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Notes, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Original, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Original, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - A Program for the American People, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - A Program for the American People, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Second Region, 1939 January; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Second Region, 1939 April; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Second Region, 1939 July; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Work Plans, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Miscellaneous, 1938-1940; 2 boxes (1 partial)
          - 1938-1939, 1 folder (Folder 1)
          - 1939 January-May, 1 folder (Folder 2)
          - 1939 September-November, 1 folder (Folder 3)
          - 1939, 1 folder (Folder 4)
          - 1939, 1 folder (Folder 1)
          - 1939-1940, 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Filing, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Financial, 1932-1939; portions of 2 boxes
        - Bills, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Checks, Cancelled, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Checks, Carbon, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Checks, Outstanding, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Statements, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Miscellaneous, 1932-1935; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Final Report of Second Region, Criticisms of, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Foreign Relations, 1938-1939; more than 3 folders
        - Meetings, 1938-1939; portion of 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Reciprocal Trade, 1938-1939; 2 folders (Folder 2 to 3)
        - Tariff, 1938-1939; portion of 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Trade Association, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Let Us Get Our Bearings, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Lists, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Meetings, 1938-1939 January; portions of 2 boxes
        - August Conference, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - August Conference, Chicago, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - August Conference, Statement Principles, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Chicago, 1938 February; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Chicago, Smith’s Remarks, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Executive Committee, 1938 May; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Foreign Affairs, 1939 January; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Regional, 1938 January; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Regional, 1938 April; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Regional, 1938 June; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Regional, One to Nine, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Second Region, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Members, Suggested, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Memoranda, 1938-1940; portions of 2 boxes
        - Farm Export Debenture Plan, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - New Jersey, 1938 January-March; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - Regional Members, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Folder 12)
        - Regional Memos, One to Thirteen,1938, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 13)
        - Regional Memos, Fourteen to Twenty-nine, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 14)
        - Regional Memos, Miscellaneous, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Republican Policy, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Moral Re-Armament, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - National Statement, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1937-1940; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Notices, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Organization and Purpose, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Party Platforms, 1932-1939; portions of 2 boxes
        - General, 1932-1938; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - General, 1938-1939; 2 folders (Folder 9 to 10)
        - Material, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - State, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Press Releases, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Public Opinion, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Publications, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Questionnaires, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Reports, 1938-1940; 5 boxes (2 partial)
        - Correspondence, 1938-1940; 3 boxes (2 partial)
          - A-B, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Folder 6)
          - B, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Folder 1)
          - C-D, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Folder 2)
          - E-F, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Folder 3)
          - G, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Folder 4)
          - H-K, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Folder 1)
          - Hoover, Herbert, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Folder 2)
          - M-P, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Folder 3)